denbroadband.in 2018-06-11

# Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

#### General Principles:

This statement discloses DEN's privacy practices, including an explanation of which personal identifiable information about the User is collected, how such information is used, with whom such information may be shared, and how the User can correct any inaccuracies in such information. Protecting Your privacy is very important to Us. DEN understands how important personal privacy is to You and We have developed this Privacy Policy to protect Your personal identifiable information and keep it confidential. We want DEN's Users to be aware of what information DEN collects and how it is handled.

We do everything We reasonably can to protect Your rights of privacy on the Websites, but are not liable for any unauthorized or unlawful disclosures of Your personal identifiable information made by third parties, who are not subject to DEN's control. However, as a pre-condition of visiting/using the Websites, you agree that DEN reserves the right to access, read, preserve, and disclose any information as it reasonably believes is necessary to preserve in order to

    1. satisfactorily comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request,
    2. enforce these Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations hereof,
    3. detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues,
    4. Individual coupon/voucher terms and conditions also apply.
    5. respond to user support requests, or
    6. protect the rights, property or safety of DEN, its users and the public. DEN will not be responsible or liable for the exercise or non-exercise of its rights under these terms and conditions.

#### Right to Collect Personal Information: 

You can visit the Websites (excluding the 'Contact Us' portion of the Websites) without revealing any information about Yourself. We shall collect information that is said to be autonomous over the DEN network. IP addresses and information collected via "Cookies" are examples of autonomous information. "Cookies" are small text files that store basic information that a Websites can use to recognize repeated visits and as an example, recall Your name if this has been previously supplied. Aggregated data is compiled into statistical and demographic information that DEN uses, and may share with others, to show preferences of its User base as a whole, but not the preferences of any individual User. Shared aggregated data does not include a level of detail that will permit anyone to identify any individual person's usage or preferences. By accepting the terms and conditions contained herein, You agree that We may collect and store Your personal information which will only be used for the purposes for which it was collected or as set out in this Privacy Policy and any other legitimate purpose.

The Websites may contain hyperlinks to websites of DEN's business partners, advertisers, sponsors and to such other websites that are not affiliated with DEN and that may or may not have similar practices in place to protect the privacy of information that You supply. DEN encourages everyone to review the privacy statements of each of the websites that are linked to or accessed from the Website so that there will be no surprise as to how each visited website collects, uses and distributes information. DEN cannot warrant the security of the information which You transmit to those websites.

#### Information Usage and Security Procedures:

By entering Your personal identifiable information, You accept that We may retain Your personal identifiable information which We may use in an aggregated format as DEN's property. We may use the information in DEN's sole discretion and without any compensation to You, for any legitimate purposes as provided in the Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy.

We are committed to the confidential treatment of all personally identifiable information received from You, both on computer servers, physically or otherwise, and secure Your personal information from unauthorized access, use and disclosure in secure environments. 

To this end, We use industry standard methods such as firewalls, encryption and system access controls, and DEN's security practices are regularly reviewed against industry best practices by internal staff and independent third parties. However, as no computer or network based product exists that can provide perfect security, DEN cannot guarantee Your information as completely risk free.

Except as otherwise noted herein, all information including the personal identifiable information and autonomous information that DEN collects when You visit/use the Websites, is used only for normal business purpose.

It is accessible by DEN employees, internal staff and installation/sales agents to the extent necessary for DEN to install, market, offer, sell, provide and monitor the technical operability of the network and/or the Websites. 

DEN also provides access of information to the extent required for the tax, legal, accounting and other professionals hired by DEN to fulfill their fiduciary or representative duty. All such professionals are bound to maintain the confidentiality of information supplied to them by contractual or ethical obligations. DEN may vary the frequency of access to information depending on its business needs which may vary from time to time.

#### General Exceptions:

If We are required to intercept, disclose, monitor and/or store Your personal information:

    1. By law;
    2. To conduct DEN's business activities;
    3. To secure DEN's systems;
    4. To enforce DEN's own rights;
    5. Market research, including statistical analysis of Your behaviour;
    6. To send You periodic communications about features, products and services, events and special offers;

We will do so in the manner as prescribed by legislation. Such interception, disclosure, monitoring and storage may take place without Your knowledge. In that case, We will not be liable to You or any third party for any damages howsoever arising from such interception, disclosure, monitoring and storage.

We will do so in the manner as prescribed by legislation. Such interception, disclosure, monitoring and storage may take place without Your knowledge. In that case, We will not be liable to You or any third party for any damages howsoever arising from such interception, disclosure, monitoring and storage.

#### Revision of the Policy:

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and You should check these regularly. Amendments to this policy will be effective when posted. Your use of the Websites will be deemed an acceptance of the existing Privacy Policy.
